Inventory of the James Robert Huntley papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- "The Bulletin of the National Association of Secondary School Principals,", 1967 (Box 174)
- China and Europe, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 175: 1)
- Benelux, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 175: 2)
- United Kingdom, 1968-1981 (Box-folder 175: 3-6)
- Sweden, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 175: 7)
- Spain, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 175: 8)
- Italy, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 175: 9)
- Japan, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 175: 10-11)
- Japan-West relations, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 175: 12)
- "The British Survey No. 233: Nationalism,", 1968 August (Box 176)
- World Survey
  - "No. 3: The Mediterranean,", 1969 March (Box 176)
  - "No. 4: American Foreign Policy,", 1969 April (Box 176)
  - "No. 5: Britain in European Organizations,", 1969 May (Box 176)
  - "No. 6: Some Caribbean Problems,", 1969 June (Box 176)
  - "No. 7: France After de Gaulle,", 1969 July (Box 176)
  - "No. 8: Eastern Europe, Political and Economic Changes,", 1969 August (Box 176)
  - "No. 9: Cuba,", 1969 September (Box 176)
  - "No. 10: Austria, South Tirol/Alto Adige,", 1969 October (Box 176)
  - "No. 11: Strategy of the Southern Oceans,", 1969 November (Box 176)
  - "No. 12: Iran,", 1969 December (Box 176)
  - "No. 13: Portugal on the Move,", 1970 January (Box 176)
  - "No. 14: Turkey,", 1970 February (Box 176)
  - "No. 15: Halting the Spread of Nuclear Weapons,", 1970 March (Box 176)
  - "No. 16: British Foreign Policy,", 1970 April (Box 176)
  - "No. 17: Belgium,", 1970 May (Box 176)
  - "No. 18: South Africa and the World,", 1970 June (Box 176)
  - "No. 19: The Philippines,", 1970 July (Box 176)
  - "No. 20: Brazil,", 1970 August (Box 176)
  - "No. 21: Italy, 1870-1970,", 1970 September (Box 176)
  - "No. 22: Iraq and the Kurds,", 1970 October (Box 176)
  - "No. 23: Strategy in South East Asia, Chinese Military Thinking,", 1970 November (Box 176)
  - "No. 24: Australia,", 1970 December (Box 176)
  - "No. 25: Yugoslavia,", 1971 January (Box 176)
  - "No. 26: Soviet Naval Expansion,", 1971 February (Box 176)
  - "No. 27: Alaska,", 1971 March (Box 176)
  - "No. 28: World Population and Food,", 1971 April (Box 176)
  - "No. 29: The Nordic Countries, Defence and Economics,", 1971 May (Box 176)
  - "No. 30: France, Britain and Europe,", 1971 June (Box 176)
  - "No. 31: The European Convention of Human Rights,", 1971 July (Box 176)
  - "No. 32: African Dialogue,", 1971 August (Box 176)
  - "No. 33: Interpol,", 1971 September (Box 176)
  - "No. 34: Mexico,", 1971 October (Box 176)
  - "No. 35: European Security,", 1971 November (Box 176)
  - "No. 36: East Germany,", 1971 December (Box 176)
  - "No. 37: The Gulf,", 1972 January (Box 176)
  - "No. 38: New Singapore,", 1972 February (Box 176)
  - "No. 39: Spain,", 1972 March (Box 176)
  - "No. 40: The Irish Question,", 1972 April (Box 176)
  - "No. 42: The American Presidential Campaign,", 1972 June (Box 176)
  - "No. 43: Hong Kong,", 1972 July (Box 176)
  - "No. 44: China Since the Cultural Revolution,", 1972 August (Box 176)
  - "No. 45: The Politics of Change, Europe 1971-72,", 1972 September (Box 176)
  - "No. 46: Guyana,", 1972 October (Box 176)
  - "No. 47: The United States Coast Guard,", 1972 November (Box 176)
  - "No. 48: Kenya,", 1972 December (Box 176)
  - "No. 49: Bangladesh,", 1973 January (Box 176)
  - "No. 51: The Law of the Sea,", 1973 March (Box 176)
  - "No. 52: Iceland,", 1973 April (Box 176)
  - "No. 53: Poland,", 1974 May (Box 176)
  - "No. 54: The Anglo-Portuguese Alliance 1373-1973,", 1973 June (Box 176)
  - "No. 55: Argentina,", 1973 July (Box 176)
  - "No. 56: The three Conferences in Europe: Talking Out the Cold War?,", 1973 August (Box 176)
  - "No. 57: The Caribbean, the Caribbean common Market and the EEC,", 1973 September (Box 176)
  - "No. 58: Southern Arabia,", 1973 October (Box 176)
  - "No. 59: Zaire, the Country and People,", 1973 November (Box 176)
  - "No. 60: Fiji,", 1973 December (Box 176)
  - "No. 61: Cyprus,", 1974 January (Box 176)
  - "No. 62: Problems of NATO 1974, Soviet Maritime Power,", 1974 February (Box 176)
  - "No. 63: Problems of NATO 1974, Defence Détente and the People,", 1974 March (Box 176)
  - "No. 64: The Maghreb,", 1974 April (Box 176)
  - "No. 65: Turkey at the Crossroads,", 1974 May (Box 176)
  - "No. 66: Korea: One People, Two Nations,", 1974 June (Box 176)
  - "No. 67: Romania,", 1974 July (Box 176)
  - "No. 78: The Atlantic Alliance: A Testing Time,", 1975 June (Box 176)
- "Crisis Paper No. 35: Portugal: A New Departure?,", 1974 May (Box 176)
- World Survey index, 1970 (Box 176)
- "History in the Making,", 1971 May-September (Box 176)
- Western European Union (WEU), 1975 (Box-folder 177: 1)
- Nordic Council, 1969 (Box-folder 177: 2)
- France, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 177: 3)
- USSR, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 177: 4)
- Germany
  - 1964 Tour, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 177: 5)
    Includes photographs.
  - South Carolina speech, 1965 (Box-folder 177: 6)
  - German Army article, 1964 (Box-folder 177: 7)
  - Health, 1959-1973 (Box-folder 177: 8)
  - General, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 177: 9-11)
- U.S.A., 1970-1974 (Box-folder 177: 12)
- Canada, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 177: 13)
- European Integration and the U.S.A., 1969-1974 (Box-folder 178: 1-3)
- European Integration, U.K. and the E.E.C., 1969-1974 (Box-folder 178: 4-6)
- Council of Europe, 1969-1982 (Box-folder 178: 7-8)
- NGOs: INSEAD (European Institute of Business Administration), 1978-1982 (Box-folder 179: 1)
- Independent Sector, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 179: 2)
- Institut für Europaische Politik, undated (Box-folder 179: 3)
- Institut International Jacques Maritain, 1982 (Box-folder 179: 4)
- Istituto Affari Internazionali, Rome, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 179: 5)
- Institute for Contemporary Studies, 1982 (Box-folder 179: 6)
- European integration
  - General, 1972-1979 (Box-folder 179: 7)
  - Cultural cooperation, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 179: 8)
  - General, 1953-1972 (Box-folder 179: 9)
  - "The Communities,", 1967-1974 (Box-folder 179: 10--12)
  - "The Triangle,", 1969-1974 (Box-folder 179: 13)
- Non-governmental organizations (NGOs)
  - Group of Thirty, 1981 (Box-folder 180: 1)
  - Institute for East-West Security Studies, 1982 (Box-folder 180: 2)
  - Institute of Economic Affairs, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 180: 3)
  - Groupe de Talloires, undated (Box-folder 180: 4)
  - The Heritage Foundation, 1982-1994 (Box-folder 180: 5)
  - Hoover Institution on War, Revolution and Peace, 1981-2002 (Box-folder 180: 6-7)
  - Howe Research Institute, 1982 (Box-folder 180: 8)
  - Hudson Institute, 1978 (Box-folder 180: 9)
  - International Institute for Democracy and Electoral Assistance (IDEA), 1997 (Box-folder 180: 10)
  - Institute for Foreign Policy Analysis, 1977-1986 (Box-folder 180: 11-12)
  - Global Resources, LTD., undated (Box-folder 181: 1)
  - Washington State Governor's School for Citizen Leadership, 1986 (Box-folder 181: 2)
  - Grand Conference Catholique, undated (Box-folder 181: 3)
  - Group for the Rational Advancement of Liberalism, undated (Box-folder 181: 4)
  - Groupement D'Etudes Politiques Européennes, undated (Box-folder 181: 5)
  - International Institute for Environment and Society, undated (Box-folder 181: 6)
  - International Institute for the Management of Technology, 1982 (Box-folder 181: 7)
  - International Institute for Strategic Studies, 1974-1992 (Box-folder 181: 8)
  - International Internship Programs, 1985 (Box-folder 181: 9)
  - International Management and Development Institute, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 181: 10)
  - International Studies Association, 1987 (Box-folder 181: 11)
  - International Association of Parliamentarians, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 181: 12)
  - International Communication Agency, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 181: 13)
  - International Crisis Group, 2000 (Box-folder 181: 14)
  - The International Council on the Future of the University, undated (Box-folder 181: 15)
  - International Development Research Center, 1987 (Box-folder 181: 16)
  - International Exchange Association, 1987 (Box-folder 181: 17)
  - International Development Law Institute, 2001 (Box-folder 181: 18)
  - International House of Japan, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 181: 19)
  - International Institute for Applied Systems Analysis, undated (Box-folder 181: 20)
  - International Institute for Democracy, Strasbourg, 1989 (Box-folder 181: 21)
  - Institute for Study of Interaction of Foreign and Domestic Affairs, 1978 (Box-folder 181: 22)
  - Institute of Turkish Studies, undated (Box-folder 181: 23)
  - Institut für Japanologie, 1980 (Box-folder 181: 24)
  - Inter-Allied Confederation of Reserve Officers, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 181: 25)
  - Interparliamentary Union, 1982 (Box-folder 181: 26)
  - International Arbeiskreis Sonnenberg, undated (Box-folder 181: 27)
  - International Association for Federal Union, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 181: 28)
  - Groupe de Paris, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 181: 29)
  - Mid-Atlantic Club
    - General, 1974-2000 (Box-folder 182: 1-2)
    - Bonn, 1982 (Box-folder 182: 3)
    - Brussels, 1982 (Box-folder 182: 4)
    - London, 1977-1996 (Box-folder 182: 5)
    - New York, 1974-1990 (Box-folder 182: 6)
    - Washington D.C., 1982-1992 (Box-folder 182: 7)
  - Minnesota International Center, 1979 (Box-folder 182: 8)
  - Minority Rights Group Ltd., 1983 (Box-folder 182: 9)
  - Mitsubishi Research Institute, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 182: 10)
  - French-American Foundation, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 182: 11)
  - Friendship Force, undated (Box-folder 182: 12)
  - George E. Taylor Foreign Affairs Institute, 1987 (Box-folder 182: 13)
  - German American Lawyers Association, undated (Box-folder 182: 14)
  - German American Partnership Program, 1983 (Box-folder 182: 15)
  - German Association for Security Policy, 1982 (Box-folder 182: 16)
  - German French Society, 1982 (Box-folder 182: 17)
  - German-Marshall Fund of the U.S., 1977-1985 (Box-folder 182: 18)
  - The German Society for Peace and Conflict Research, 1975-1982 (Box-folder 182: 19)
  - USIA- German-U.S. Bilateral Commission, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 182: 20)
  - Global Economic Action Institute, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 182: 21)
  - Global Futures Network, Inc., 1981 (Box-folder 182: 22)
  - Japan-America Society of the State of Washington, 1975-1982 (Box-folder 183: 1)
  - Japan-California Association, 1976-1983 (Box-folder 183: 2)
  - Japan Center of Security Issues, undated (Box-folder 183: 3)
  - The Japan Foundation, 1982 (Box-folder 183: 4)
  - Japan Institute for International Study, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 183: 5)
  - Japan Institute of International Affairs, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 183: 6)
  - Japan Productivity Center, 1982 (Box-folder 183: 7)
  - Japan Society, New York, 1973-1982 (Box-folder 183: 8)
  - Japan-U.S. Economic Relations Group, undated (Box-folder 183: 9)
  - Japan-U.S. Friendship Commission, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 183: 10)
  - Jean Monet Council, 1990 (Box-folder 183: 11)
  - Jeunesse Ouvrière Chrétienne Internationale, 1982 (Box-folder 183: 12)
  - John Hopkins University Bologna Center, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 183: 13)
  - Keidanren, undated (Box-folder 183: 14)
  - Kosomol, undated (Box-folder 183: 15)
  - Kyodai, 1978 (Box-folder 183: 16)
  - Kezai Doyukai, undated (Box-folder 183: 17)
  - John F. Kennedy Institute, 1980-1988 (Box-folder 183: 18)
  - KRAB Radio, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 183: 19)
  - Lehrman Institute, 1977 (Box-folder 183: 20)
  - Lesli Sawhny Program, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 183: 21)
  - Liberal International, 1981 (Box-folder 183: 22)
  - LUISS University, undated (Box-folder 183: 23)
  - The Marshall Group, 1984 (Box-folder 183: 24)
  - Matsushita Leadership Report, 1981 (Box-folder 183: 25)
  - Micronesia Institute, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 183: 26)
  - World Politics Assorted Materials, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 184: 1)
  - Committees for a Community of Democracies, 1982-198 (Box-folder 184: 2)
  - Committees for a Community of Democracies, tenets and objectives, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 184: 3)
  - Atlantic Organizations, 1973-1990 (Box-folder 184: 4)
  - International University Nigata, undated (Box-folder 184: 5)
  - Istituto Per Gli Studi Di Politica Internazionale, 1982 (Box-folder 184: 6)
  - Istituto Carlo Cattaneo, 1982 (Box-folder 184: 7)
  - James Madison Institute, 1989 (Box-folder 184: 8)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange, 1975-2001 (Box-folder 184: 9-11)
- Asian Development Bank, 1973-1995 (Box-folder 185: 1)
- South Asian Association for Regional Cooperation (SAARC), 1985 (Box-folder 185: 2)
- Australia, 1974-1997 (Box-folder 185: 3-5)
- India, 1990-2001 (Box-folder 185: 6)
- International system, 1964-1976 (Box-folder 185: 7-8)
- Africa, 1974-1991 (Box-folder 186: 1)
- African Union, 2002 (Box-folder 186: 2)
- South Africa, 1986-1994 (Box-folder 186: 3)
- Nigeria, 1979-1992 (Box-folder 186: 4)
- Asia, General, 1974-2000 (Box-folder 186: 5-6)
- Association of South East Asian Nations (ASEAN), 1975-1977 (Box-folder 186: 7)
- ASEAN, 1977-2001 (Box-folder 186: 8-9)
- Egypt, 1976-1992 (Box-folder 186: 10)
- Algeria, 1996 (Box-folder 186: 11)
- Germany, 1980-1990 (Box-folder 187: 1-5)
- Germany, 1990-2004 (Box-folder 188: 1-4)
- France, 1967-1979 (Box-folder 188: 5-6)
- Ireland, 1974-1991 (Box-folder 189: 1)
- New Zealand, 1975-2001 (Box-folder 189: 2)
- Australia, 2003 (Box-folder 189: 3)
- Malaysia, 1986 (Box-folder 189: 4)
- Taiwan, 1974-2003 (Box-folder 189: 5)
- France, 1981-2004 (Box-folder 189: 6-8)
- Thailand, 1974-1992 (Box-folder 189: 9)
- Vietnam, 1986 (Box-folder 189: 10)
- Western Europe, 1975-1982 (Box-folder 189: 11)
- Austria, 1975-2000 (Box-folder 189: 12)
- Belgium and the Netherlands, 1971-1987 (Box-folder 189: 13)
- Indonesia, 1990-1997 (Box-folder 189: 14)
- The Philippines, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 189: 15)
- Battelle Institute Comprehensive Plan, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 190: 1-2)
- Battelle Institute Land Trust, 1993-2000 (Box-folder 190: 3)
- Gazzam Lake, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 190: 4-5)
- Bainbridge Island Civic Matters, 1989-2000 (Box-folder 190: 6)
- United Kingdom, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 190: 7-8)
- Bainbridge Island Land Trust, board members notebook, 1995 (Box-folder 191: 1-3)
- The Atlantic Community Quarterly, Vol. 10 to 15, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 191: 4-9)
- The Atlantic Community Quarterly, Vol. 10 to 15 (Contd.), 1972-1977 (Box-folder 192: 1-13)
- "The Technologists,", 1967-1973 (Box-folder 193: 1)
- Elites and leadership, 1957-1978 (Box-folder 193: 2)
- Work and motivation, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 193: 3)
- University of Sussex: Science Policy Research Unit, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 193: 4)
- Change, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 193: 5)
- Bainbridge Island Committee to Save DNR Forest, 1991 (Box-folder 193: 6)
- Voters Initiative (Robert Adams), 1989-1991 (Box-folder 193: 7)
- Appeals Against Pacesetter Case, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 193: 8-9)
- Campus unrest, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 194: 1-2)
- Student unrest, 1969 (Box-folder 194: 3)
- Youth unrest, 1966-1974 (Box-folder 194: 4)
- Science policy, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 194: 5-6)
- International communications, 1974 (Box-folder 195: 1)
- Computers, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 195: 2)
- Americans overseas, stateless peoples, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 195: 3)
- Futurology, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 195: 4)
- Nature of man, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 195: 5)
- General crisis, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 195: 6)
- Social breakdown, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 195: 7)
- Intelligence and ability, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 195: 8)
- Mass media, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 195: 9)
- Language and lexicography, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 195: 10)
- Youth
  - Council of Europe, 1969 (Box-folder 195: 11-13)
  - European communities, 1970 (Box-folder 195: 14)
- "The Atlantic Papers 1: Scandinavia Faces Europe,", 1973 (Box 196)
- "The Atlantic Papers 2: The Canadian Dilemma,", 1973 (Box 196)
- "The Atlantic Papers 3: Japan and the Atlantic World,", 1972 (Box 196)
- The Atlantic Community Quarterly, Vol. 14 to 18, 1980 (Box 196)
- Youth
  - Generation gap and elders, 1969-1979 (Box-folder 197: 1-2)
  - Schools, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 197: 3)
  - Television, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 197: 4)
  - Council of Europe Youth Center and Foundation, 1963-1969 (Box-folder 197: 5-6)
  - Opinion polls, 1966-1979 (Box-folder 197: 7-8)
- Democracy, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 197: 9)
- Far Right, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 197: 10)
- New Left, 1970-1979 (Box-folder 197: 11)
- Youth, military and national service, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 197: 12)
- Youth, non-student violence, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 197: 13)
- Correspondence, 1997 (Box-folder 198: 1-2)
- Public Opinion, Vol. 7 to 10, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 198: 3-7)
- The Federalist: A Political Review, Year XXXI to XXXII and XL, 1989-1990, 1998 (Box-folder 198: 8-12)
- The Atlantic Papers
  - "No. 35: Europe and the North-South Dialogue,", 1978 (Box-folder 198: 13)
  - "No. 2: First World Relationships: The Role of the OECD,", 1975 (Box-folder 198: 14)
  - "No. 1: European Agriculture in an Uncertain World,", 1975 (Box-folder 198: 15)
  - "No. 4: Spotlights on Inflation,", 1974 (Box-folder 198: 16)
  - "No. 3: Toward a New International Economic Order,", 1974 (Box-folder 198: 17)
  - "No. 4: Europe and America: From Alliance to Coalition,", 1973 (Box-folder 198: 18)
  - "No. 3: Two Germanys in One World,", 1973 (Box-folder 198: 19)
- Correspondence
  - 1995 (Box-folder 199: 1-2)
  - 1996 (Box-folder 199: 3-4)
  - 1998 (Box-folder 199: 5-6)
  - 1993 (Box-folder 200: 1-3)
  - 1994 (Box-folder 200: 4-6)
  - 1992 (Box-folder 201: 1-3)
  - 1993 (Box-folder 201: 4-5)
  - 1993 January (Box-folder 201: 6)
- Ost-Asien Institut, 1982 (Box-folder 202: 1)
- Pacific Basin Economic Council (PBEC), 1957-1973 (Box-folder 202: 2)
- Transnational Associations, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 202: 3)
- Assorted publications, 1981-1991 (Box-folder 202: 4)
- Social Fabric of Community, 1985 (Box-folder 202: 5)
- U.S. Commitment to Europe, 1982 (Box-folder 202: 6)
- NATO 40th Anniversary, 1989 (Box-folder 202: 7)
- Youth
  - Cultural revolution, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 202: 8-9)
  - Drugs, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 202: 10-11)
  - International ties, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 202: 12)
- The Monday Club, London, undated (Box-folder 203: 1)
- Mondoperaio, 1982 (Box-folder 203: 2)
- Moral Re-Armament, 1988-1997 (Box-folder 203: 3)
- Movimento Culturale di Impegno Atlantico, undated (Box-folder 203: 4)
- Il Mulino, 1982 (Box-folder 203: 5)
- Multilateral Policy Council, 1984 (Box-folder 203: 6)
- National Council for International Visitors (NCIV), 1979-1986 (Box-folder 203: 7)
- National Council of World Affairs Organizations, 1998 (Box-folder 203: 8)
- Netherlands Institute of International Relations, 1982 (Box-folder 203: 9)
- Netherlands Institute for Peace Research, 1982 (Box-folder 203: 10)
- New Directions, 1977 (Box-folder 203: 11)
- Niagra Institute for International Studies, 1976-1983 (Box-folder 203: 12)
- Nomura Research Institute, 1982 (Box-folder 203: 13)
- The Norway-America Association, 1974-1982 (Box-folder 203: 14)
- The Norwegian Atlantic Committee Publications, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 203: 15-16)
- The Pacific Institute, Australia, 1976-1990 (Box-folder 203: 17-18)
- Social Science Research Council, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 204: 1)
- Socialist International, 1983 (Box-folder 204: 2)
- Societé Italiana Per L'Organizzazione Internazionale, 1982 (Box-folder 204: 3)
- Svaz Pratelu USA (SPUSA), Czechoslovak, 1990 (Box-folder 204: 4)
- The Standing Conference of Atlantic Organizations (SCAO)
  - General, 1971-1998 (Box-folder 204: 5-6)
  - Newsletter, 1977-1999 (Box-folder 204: 7)
  - Meetings, 1977-1990 (Box-folder 204: 8)
  - "The Western World and the Will to Survive," report, 1977 (Box-folder 204: 9)
  - General, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 204: 10)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 204: 11)
- National Defense University, 1981 (Box-folder 204: 12)
- National Institute for Research Advancement, undated (Box-folder 204: 13)
- National Peace Academy, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 204: 14)
- National Strategy Information Center, 1981-1987 (Box-folder 204: 15)
- Navy League of Australia, undated (Box-folder 204: 16)
- CSIS Quadrangular Forum, 1986 (Box-folder 205: 1)
- The Western World Book Review, 1983 (Box-folder 205: 2)
- Research Institute for Peace and Security, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 205: 3)
- Roosevelt Center for American Policy Studies, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 205: 4)
- Royal United Services Institute of Australia, undated (Box-folder 205: 5)
- Royal United Services Institute for Defence Studies, 1982 (Box-folder 205: 6)
- Royal Institute of International Affairs, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 205: 7)
- Royal Overseas League, undated (Box-folder 205: 8)
- Salzburg Seminar on American Studies, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 205: 9)
- Sankei Shimbun Institute, undated (Box-folder 205: 10)
- National Council of World Affairs Organizations, 1974-1981 (Box-folder 205: 11)
- Science Policy Foundation, 1979 (Box-folder 205: 12)
- Seattle Chamber of Commerce, 1976 (Box-folder 205: 13)
- The Seattle Committee on Foreign Relations, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 205: 14)
- Seidl-Stiftung, undated (Box-folder 205: 15)
- Society for Intercultural Education, Training and Research (SIETAR), 1973-1982 (Box-folder 205: 16-17)
- Sister Cities International, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 205: 18)
- Strategic Studies Institute, undated (Box-folder 206: 1)
- Suntory Foundation, undated (Box-folder 206: 2)
- Telders Foundation, 1982 (Box-folder 206: 3)
- Teldersstichting, undated (Box-folder 206: 4)
- Thomas Jefferson Research Center, 1982 (Box-folder 206: 5)
- Tocqueville Center, New York, 1969, 1982 (Box-folder 206: 6)
- Tokyo Group, undated (Box-folder 206: 7)
- Trade Policy Research Center, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 206: 8)
- Trans Atlantic Studies Association, 2002 (Box-folder 206: 9)
- Translation Service Center, 1979 (Box-folder 206: 10)
- Pacific Basin Institute, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 206: 11)
- Pacific Cooperation Committee, 1982 (Box-folder 206: 12)
- Pacific Democrat Union, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 206: 13)
- Pacific Economic Cooperation, 1986 (Box-folder 206: 14)
- Pacific Forum, undated (Box-folder 206: 15)
- Pacific Northwest NGOs, 1971-1988 (Box-folder 206: 16)
- Pacific Ocean Policy Studies, 1984 (Box-folder 206: 17)
- Partners of the Americas, undated (Box-folder 206: 18)
- Peace Through NATO, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 206: 19)
- People to People International, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 206: 20)
- Physicians for Social Responsibility, 1981 (Box-folder 206: 21)
- The Pilgrims of Great Britain, undated (Box-folder 206: 22)
- Policy Studies Institute, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 206: 23)
- Port of Seattle, 1977 (Box-folder 206: 24)
- Productivity Promotion Council, undated (Box-folder 206: 25)
- Programme for Strategic and International Security Studies, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 206: 26)
- Program on Non-Profit Organizations, Yale University, 1986 (Box-folder 206: 27)
- Public Diplomacy Council, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 206: 28)
- Institute of Current World Affairs, 1978-1992 (Box-folder 207: 1-2)
- Pacific Rim Project, University of Washington, 1978 (Box-folder 207: 3)
- University of Washington
  - Cultural and Intercultural Education, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 207: 4)
  - School of International Studies, 1975-1982 (Box-folder 207: 5)
  - Colloquium on Security Studies, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 207: 6)
- Hartford Foundation, 1982 (Box-folder 207: 7)
- Victoria League for Commonwealth Friendship, undated (Box-folder 207: 8)
- Villa Serbelloni, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 207: 9)
- United States Institute of Peace, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 207: 10)
- United Nations University, 1978 (Box-folder 207: 11)
- United States International University, 1982 (Box-folder 207: 12)
- United World College, undated (Box-folder 207: 13)
- University Association for Contemporary European Studies, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 207: 14)
- University of Washington, Center for West European Studies, 1978-1996 (Box-folder 207: 15)
- Universities Field Staff International, 1982 (Box-folder 207: 16)
- Université de la Paix, 1999 (Box-folder 207: 17)
- Stanford Research Institute, 1975 (Box-folder 207: 18)